He won't fail, so why would, why would He bail out? He won't, yeah. He won't, He won't, He won't, He won't, He won't fail. He won't fail.
give generously to his kingdom work. As we give, we remind ourselves that everything we have already belongs to God, and we grow in our joy and our faith. The Apostle Paul wrote this to the Corinthian church in 2 Corinthians 9, 10-11. Now the one who provides seed for the sower and bread for food will also provide and multiply your seed and increase the harvest of your righteousness.
Hill near Stonehenge trying to figure out all they can about these big rocks and about life around those rocks until recently a group of geologists discovered that the archaeologists were excavating the wrong hill. For 90 years they had been digging on the wrong hill and the geologists they realized that they were gonna this was gonna be very frustrating to hear in fact Richard Bevans was one of the geologists and he said this I don't expect to be getting Christmas cards from the archaeologists who've been excavating at the wrong place over all these years. 90 years of digging on the wrong hill the hill they were supposed to be digging from was about a mile away. Imagine if you were a guy named Rick and Rick as Rick you worked on that hill you grew up as a kid and your dad was an archaeologist and your dad dreamed of being able to work on Stonehenge there were pictures of Stonehenge all in your house when you were a child and you went to high school and you loved rocks and figuring out all the different rock formations you went to college and you became an archaeologist and right out of college you were offered this light this dream job the dream job of a lifetime for you to work on the with a group of people that were excavating around Stonehenge and you took this job and you were there your entire career every day that you went to work you went to this hill and you dug on this hill trying to figure out all you could about Stonehenge you got married you had kids and your kids were so proud of what you did they invited you to their science class and every year you go to science class and you would give pictures of Stonehenge and you would talk about what you were doing you at your house you also had lots of pictures of Stonehenge and at dinner parties you would drop random facts about Stonehenge when you were really proud of what you were doing 40 years of a career and then you find out at the end of your career that you have been digging on the wrong hill your entire career
career, perhaps you would think, what was this for? Did I waste all of my life? What was this for? I was digging on the wrong hill the entire time.
Book of Ecclesiastes is actually inspiring to read because this book understands the complexities and the pain of life. And so I want to jump in right away because we're going to spend today in the first two chapters of Ecclesiastes. We're looking for meaning in life because some of you are worried that you're digging on the wrong hill. And so if you have an opportunity, you can text guide to the number on your screen.
In fact, when he became king, God asked him, what do you want? You can ask me for anything. And Solomon said, I would like wisdom. God was like, wow, you didn't ask for me to kill all of your enemies.
This is used 40 times, and this word is used throughout as well. And what it means is the end result, the profit. So what's the bottom line for life? After all that you've accomplished, all that you've achieved, acquired, the hill that you dug on for all of your life, what really is the gain?
And those people are gone, but the views remain. He's saying, really? You actually think you have a bottom line in life? You are so temporary.
going into the ocean. And he said, and I had been reading Ecclesiastes on that trip, and so it just stung as he said it. He said, this water right now that is going from this waterfall into the ocean, it started on the north shore of the island 30 years ago. And 30 years it takes for this stream, for the water in the stream to go all throughout the island and make its way here to the Nepali coast and hit.
and connected, we are perhaps more efficient at those things, but the desires beneath the surface are still the same. There's nothing really new under the sun. The desires for community, the desires for more information, and the need to transport from one place to another, those have always existed. Verse 11, there is no remembrance of those who came before and of those who will come after.